[Skip To Content](javascript:void(0);)

We Care About Your Privacy
==========================

Our Privacy Policy explains what information we process when you use Max and describes how that information is collected and used. It also includes details about your rights and how to contact us. The Supplement provides additional information for residents of certain states and countries. Our Ad Choices site provides you more information about choices that you have for targeted advertising.

North America (United States)
-----------------------------

### Privacy Policy

[English](https://www.hbomax.com/privacy/en-us "North America (United States) - English Privacy Policy")

[Español](https://www.hbomax.com/privacy/es-us "North America (United States) - Spanish Privacy Policy")

### US State Supplement

[English](https://www.hbomax.com/privacy/usrights/en-us "North America (United States) - English US State Supplement")

[Español](https://www.hbomax.com/privacy/usrights/es-us "North America (United States) - Spanish US State Supplement")

### Ad Choices

[English](https://www.warnermediaprivacy.com/opt-out/ "North America (United States) - English Ad Choices")

[Español](https://www.warnermediaprivacy.com/opt-out/?lang=es "North America (United States) - Spanish Ad Choices")

Latin America & Caribbean
-------------------------

### Privacy Policy

### Legal Bases Chart

Europe
------

### Privacy Policy

### Legal Bases Chart

Asia Pacific
------------

### Privacy Policy

### Legal Bases Chart

©2024 WarnerMedia Direct, LLC. All Rights Reserved. Max is used under license.
